[{"answer": "We worked it out when he was trying to run me out of town.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "... in this dysfunctional Washington?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, people have been asking me that question for as long as I can remember.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Have you ever thought of, you know, running for high office?", "qSentId": 17}, {"answer": "Basically, it's a pretty equal distribution.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Who wins?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "Day after tomorrow, my wife because she has had more experience, all the long run.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "What do you think might make the better president, your wife or your daughter?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Oh, look, you always have to say there's a possibility of a health problem and accident, something you can't imagine.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "In terms of Hillary, do you think there's any doubt that Hillary will run for the presidency in 2016?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "No, I think -- I don't think that's part of my immediate future.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "And there's a tiny little part of you think to yourself Gingrich v Clinton, let's get it all over again?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "You'll have to ask her that.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Before we get too deep into the weeds, is your mom running for president?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Well, I think, you know, I would have to agree with Chelsea I think that young people are doing extraordinary thing from this country and the misperception is that young people are disconnected and disengaged and while they're might be some truth to that in statistics what I see and I'm sure what Chelsea sees and what Peggy sees globally is that young people are passionate, and ready, and primed, and every single one of them capable of caring and capable of taking action.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "What are the key issues facing particularly young woman in America right now?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "You know, we could probably make an exception.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Do I have a prayer on that or am I done?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "I mean, I think it's deplorable.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "What is your reaction to what happened that having talked to people back in Kenya?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "I mean the greatest risk factor arguably is in unemployed young men to any social system, to any society anywhere in the world.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "How do you think you could get bags (ph) of experience to deal parents in this area but how do you think the best way for a country like America can actually deal with this kind of problem?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Well, Piers people have been asking me that question for as long as I can remember.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Have you ever thought of running for high office?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Well the truthful answer is thankfully the truthful answer I guess and that I'm deeply grateful for my life now.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "What the truthful answer?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "I'm deeply inspired by my parents and I'm deeply inspired by the facts that they have always denominated success in their lives by the impact that they've had in the public sector and the non-profit sector.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Have you been inspired or deterred by what's happened to your incredibly successful parents?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "America.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "So how do we and are you attending to that?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "We get invited into people lives about 1.8 billion times a day.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "How many cans of coke do you sell a year?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "A day.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "A day?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "There are few.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "How many people -- I've always wanted to ask you this, how many people know the exact final recipe with all ingredients for Coca Cola?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "... and we don't always travel together, so that's -- look.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "How many?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Well, I think as Chelsea and America and one of your earlier panelists had said the best.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "That's an interesting issue because I think, John, you have the same don't you in Cisco?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "That goes in life with that?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Well, I think both Muhtar and John are examples of a moral capitalism in their own stories as they just relate, you know, whether it is Coca-Cola's clear commitment to clean water because I imagine, whatever the secret ingredients are and the super secret recipe, water is one of them.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Is there a moral capitalism ahead where American global companies should bring more jobs back to America?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "HELSEA CLINTON: No.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "He didn't even flicker, did you see that?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "He didn't even confirm water.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "He wouldn't even confirm water?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Well, let me ask you (inaudible), it's a serious issue isn't it?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Oh, we play Pinochle, spades, hearts, all variant ...", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Which card games?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Thankfully, it's a pretty equal distribution.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Who wins?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "It's true.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "How did I know you'd say that?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "So, in cards probably.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "You tell me, you all win 33 percent of the time, right?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "I do really well in the traditional board games, backgammon, checkers.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "What are you best at?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "I'm still on cloud nine, haven't touched down yet.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Let me start with you Shannon, how does that make you guys feel?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I think it's innate personally, when we're down 6-1 that was we just -- we didn't have any boats and we're -- and it felt like we would never had a chance.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "What was the thinking in the group of that moment when you really were staring a huge defeat in the face?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "To win the America's Cup it's a hard slug (ph) over three years for us in this campaign and then to get at the end of the -- to it to get so far behind and made it even harder.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Joe Spooner, what does it take to win the America's Cup particularly when you're coming from so far behind?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "I don't think for anyone in the team is really dawned on us when we have a chance, you know, it's -- be standing to hear these comments about a great comeback and maybe one of the greatest that, you know, setting an sailing team in world sport it's just incredible.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "What is your reaction to him bestowing you the accolade there that he did?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely we have Rome Kirby he's the young American in our team, we have John Kostecki he's our American technician on the boat and of course there's a huge American culture within the team and I think, you know, we lift the American dream, never give up, keep fighting, forward look at the goal and we did it and yes, it has been great.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Are any of you guys actually American on the squad?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "130926pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Congratulations and I would imagine you're going to go and have one almighty party, aren't you?", "qSentId": 525}]